Yahoo.
やっほー
Hello.
こんにちは
It's been a while.
久しぶりだね
久しぶりです
How long has it been?
どんくらいぶり?
More than half a year.
半年以上
It's been over half a year.
半年以上ぶりくらいだね
It's kind of like that, my hair color is back again.
なんかあれだね、髪色また戻したの
Did you return it?
戻しました?
hey.
ね
After all, blonde hair was no good, right?
やっぱり金髪ダメだった?
My blonde hair just doesn't need enough care.
金髪ちょっとケアが足りないです
Seriously?
マジで?
Seriously.
マジで
I've heard that the blonde Saya-chan is nice too.
金髪のさやちゃんもいいねっていう声はあったけどさ
Oh, sure.
ああ、確かに
There were a lot of black-haired people who thought black hair was really nice.
黒髪の、黒髪がやっぱいいねっていう風なのが多かったよね
He was watching me properly.
ちゃんと見てくれてんだ
Did you see it?
見ました?
A lot of comments.
コメントめっちゃ
Did you see it?
見てた?
yes.
はい
Viewers, please leave lots of comments.
視聴者さん、いっぱいコメントしてあげてくださいね、
This hair.
この髪
What do you want to see?
どういうのが見たいってね
I certainly want that.
確かにそれは欲しい
I want it.
欲しいよね
hey.
ね
Do you remember last year when I took an outdoor photo?
覚えてるかな、去年、屋外の撮った時さ、
Do you remember what you said to your uncle?
おじさんに言った言葉覚えてるの?
Uncle, at that time, it was a shame.
おじさん、その時さ、くすじょく的でさ
No, no, last year, when was it?
いや、いや、去年さ、いつだったっけな、
I think it was around last summer.
去年の夏ぐらいだったかな
Sometimes, we filmed 4P.
時にさ、4P撮ったじゃん
At that time, there was a lot of buzz about that work with the uncle 4P.
その時にさ、おじさん4Pでさ、結構あの作品バズったじゃん
However, when I took a picture outdoors, an old man said,
だけどさ、屋外撮った時にさ、おじさんにさ、
No, that 4P wasn't enough.
いや、あの4Pじゃちょっと足りなかったんです
I said I didn't have enough.
もの足りなかったですって言ったのさ、
You're a bit of an old man.
ちょっとおじさん、くすじょく的でさ
So, today I was wondering how many people would gather.
だからさ、今日はね、どんぐらい集まるもんなんだろうと思って
Well, I hid my voice from one end.
さ、 片っ端から声を隠させていただきました
For Sena-chan.
セナちゃんのためにね
Sena-chan, by the way, that's it.
セナちゃん、ちなみにあれでしょ
You like dicks, right?
おちんちゃん好きなんでしょ
I like it.
好きです
I like all kinds of dicks.
いろんなおちんちゃん好きなんだよね
Such a cute face.
こんな可愛い顔でさ
picture?
え?
You like dicks, right?
おちんちゃん好きなんでしょ
Looks like a beautiful woman.
美女みたい
Is it true?
本当ですか?
everytime?
いつも?
Always.
いつもですって
Have you lost weight?
なんかさ、痩せた?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
lie?
う そ?
Hey, just give it a try.
ちょっとじゃあ、ちょっとやってみてよ
Hey, you've lost weight.
ね え、痩せたよね
why?
なんで?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Because it's summer.
夏だから
Are you sick?
病んだの?
I'm not sick.
病んでない
It's like, it's been a long time, what is it?
なんかさ、なんか前さ、なんだっけ?
I heard some fans shout out to me.
なんかファンに声かけられたんだよね
Oh, yes.
え、そう
I was told.
言われました
I guess some of the fans were calling out to you.
なんかファンに声かけられたんでしょ
In one word.
一言で
If there are a lot of people, then there must be fans in that area.
いっぱいじゃあ、その辺にファンがいるんだね
Dad is happy.
パパ嬉しいです
happy?
嬉しい?
A fan called out to me, Sena-chan.
ファンに声かけられてさ、 せなちゃん、
I saw the video.
動画見ましたよ
When I was asked to do it with my uncle,
おじさんともやってよって言われたら、
What should I do?
どうすんの?
think.
考える
think?
考える?
Well, by all means.
じゃあ、ぜひ
Please just stop searching.
探すのだけはやめてあげてください
I wish you wouldn't do Seninzaka, but...
せんいん坂ちょっとしないでほしいけど、
On the way, if we bump into each other on the street,
途中でね、道でばったり会っちゃったら、
Shout out to me.
声かけて
Think about it.
考えるんだ
I'll think about it.
考えます
If you think that's your type,
もしあれだ、自分のタイプだなと思ったら、
That means there's a chance you might get eaten.
食らえちゃう可能性もあるってことだね
Maybe so.
そうかもしれない
He's such a pervert.
こんな変態野郎ですね
Well then, what did we gather for today?
じゃあね、今日は、 何に集まったんでしょうって言うのでね、
I'll be waiting a little behind you,
ちょっと後ろ、いっぱい待機してるんで、
You were surprised, right?
びっくりしたでしょ?
A lot.
だいぶ
That's a lot, isn't it?
だいぶでしょ
Of course, but this is my first experience.
もちろんだけど、初めての経験だよね
Of course not.
さすがにないね
You don't know what will happen.
どうなるかわかんないでしょ
Well then, welcome to Ochinchinranday.
じゃあ、おちんちんランデーようこそ
yes.
はい
There are various rides, so please enjoy them.
いろんな乗り物あるんで、楽しんでてください
Today's penis lunch.
今日のおちんちんランデー
Well then, everyone please.
じゃあ、みなさんどうぞ
You look happy.
うれしそうだね
How many people will come?
何人来るんですか?
Something like that.
みたいなね
picture?
え?
Chair wear?
椅子着?
I'm wearing a chair.
椅子着なんだよ
私、椅子着です
Now, please count how many people there are.
じゃあ、何人か数えてみてください
9 people.
9人
What does that mean?
ってことは?
10P
It's 10P.
10Pですね
Isn't it?
ないでしょ?
No.
ないです
4P wasn't enough, right?
4Pじゃだって物足りなかったんでしょ?
Well, well, well.
まあまあまあ
Right?
でしょ?
So isn't it enough?
だからもう物足りないですか?
No, but I thought it would be at least 6 minutes.
いや、でもせめて6分かと思ってたら
I'd like to add about two people.
ちょっと2人くらい足してみたいな
I was thinking of adding one or two people.
1人1人2人くらい足してみたいな思ってたら
That old man is not sweet.
そんなおちさん甘くないよ
So, let's all take a commemorative photo together.
じゃあ、みんなで記念撮影しようか
Commemorative photo?
記念撮影?
Shall we take a commemorative photo?
記念写真撮ろうか
Everyone please look at me.
みんなこっち見てもらって
Yes, peace.
はい、ピース
nice.
いいね
Useme-chan looks happy.
うせめちゃん、うれしそうだね
As expected.
やっぱりね
It's interesting.
面白くて
interesting?
面白い?
Useme-chan, turn to me and make a peace.
うせめちゃん、こっち向いてピースしてよ
Yes, then this is a thumbnail advertisement.
はい、じゃあこれサムネ広報です
copper?
どう?
I want to be there on the right, and I want to be on the left too.
右もいて、左もいてみたいな
There are others behind me.
後ろもいる
It looks like there are others behind me.
後 ろ もいるみたいな
But no matter where you touch it, it's tiny.
だけど、どこ触ってもちびちんだからさ
This might be Pilon.
こんなのピロンかも
I will do my best?
頑張ります?
Please enjoy.
楽しんでてください
I will enjoy it.
楽しませていただきます
Please enjoy.
楽しんでてください
Well then, let's get started.
じゃあ、いざ開幕ということで
Sorry, I don't have any participants.
すみません、参入者は持たないので
Is it okay if I come suddenly?
急にいれば大丈夫?
Not enough.
足りない
Maybe I'm not enough.
私が足りないかもしれない
If I need something suddenly, I want something that I don't have enough of.
急にいれば足りない方が欲しいんだよ
Well, I have enough for two people.
じゃあ私、2人分ぐらい
Let me know your thoughts later.
後で感想聞かせて
yes.
はい
I'm not really paying attention.
さすがに注視してない
That's what I'm not paying close attention to.
注視してないとこだ
Next time.
次はね
Isn't that what you were paying attention to?
注視したものでしょ?
I want to keep an eye on it.
注視したいとこだ
I want to keep an eye on it
注 視したい
That's what I heard.
と こだ
What I know is already bad.
知っているものがすでに良くない
It's cute, but I guess it's kind of see-soo.
可愛いけど、シースーな感じかな
It's being ignored.
無視されてるよ
being ignored
無視されてる
Yo.
よ
I'm pushing up.
オ ラオラ押し上げてる
押し上げてる
I'm pushing up.
This is it, everyone.
これ ね、みんなね
Seira-chan, everyone.
せいらちゃん、みんなね
Please show me your amazing pussy.
すごいマンコウ見せてくださいとかさ
It's so loud, guys.
すごいうるさいんだよ、みんな
Really.
本当に
It's like Izamai.
いざまいみたい
That's why I'm going to open this a lot.
だから、いっぱいこれ開くからさ
I'll take a lot of this.
いっぱい取るからね、これ
Right away, this.
すぐね、これ
Yeah.
うん
DM me and he'll come too.
DMで彼も来るからさ
That's right.
そうね
I want to see a manfish.
マンコウ見たいな
Let me take a look at your pussy.
ちょっとマンコウ見してあげて
Just a little pussy, give me a little more time.
ちょっとマンコウとさ、もうちょっと時間見せてあげて
Take it away a little more.
もうちょっと取り捨てて
Now spread your pussy even more,
今さ、もっとマンコウ広げてあげて、
Girlfriend.
彼女さん
Tell the manfish to see you.
マンコウにお目つかって言ってさ
Wake up the situation a little more.
もうちょっと状態を起こして
Spread the pussy, put it on the club,
マンコウ広げて、クラブに置いて、
Please show me the camera.
ちゃんとカメラ見せてあげて
Spread it out.
広げて
You can do it yourself.
自分でやってもいいよ
Nice to meet you.
よろしくね
It's kind of increased.
なんか増えてきた
Move.
引っ越して
Oh yeah, spread it out.
そうそう、広げてあげて
By all means.
どうしてもいって
Good luck and do your best.
カッコンで頑張って
Please come here too.
こっちもいってね
Give it to me in a cool way.
カッコンであげて
yes.
そう
Give it to me with your dick.
ちんこでカッコンであげて
I'm busy.
忙しいんだよ
There's a man going around, right?
男の人が回っているでしょ
Go to yourself.
自分に回っていって
Here.
こ っち
It was over there.
あっちだった
There are a lot of dicks out there, right?
いっぱいマンチンちんこいるでしょ
Hey, should I go to sleep?
ちょ、寝ちゃうか
Let's do two at the same time.
2本同時にやってもらおう
yes.
はい
oh yeah.
そうそう
We're doing it at the same time.
同時にやってるんだよ
Combine the two.
2本合わせて
enter?
入る?
Feeling.
きめき
Maybe even more.
一層かも
Can I take it out?
出していい?
Yeah.
うん
I'll take it out.
出しちゃうよ
I went right away because it was early.
早いからすぐ行っちゃったんだよ
Clean up.
お掃除して
once again.
もう一度
Something I haven't seen in a while.
久しぶりのやつ
I'll come in.
入るよ
You look happy.
嬉しそうだね
It seems like it's finally here.
やっとかみたいな
Yeah, what happened?
うん、どうしたの?
Sayuto remained surprised.
さゆとはびっくりしたのまま
I'm going to cum inside you.
中に出しちゃうよ
I'll show it on my face.
顔に出しちゃう
It feels good, Suzuzu.
気持ちいいよ、すぎず
I'll go.
行くよ
Let me out.
出してよ
grab hands and mouth
手と口つかむ
hey.
ね
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Let's get the sperm out.
精子出そう
I'll put it out.
出すよ
tired.
疲れた
amazing.
すごい
terrible.
やばい
Were you satisfied?
満足できた?
Just for yourself.
ちょっと自分で
excitement
き めき
Can you do it?
ちゃん できる?
Kimeki-chan.
き め きちゃん
Awesome.
すっごい
Yeah.
うん
Wait a minute.
ちょぐちょ
Were you satisfied?
満足できましたか?
Yeah.
うん
still?
まだ?
As it is?
それなりに?
Let's go.
せっ
Were you reasonably satisfied?
それなりに満足できた?
It's still a hit, so.
まだで当たりますよ、だから
Shall we take a short break and continue?
ちょっと一回休憩して、続きやろうか、
and.
そして
One more time, about 10 more times.
もう一回、もう10回ぐらい
Like that.
そんな感じで